booksdescr.com 2019-04-04

# booksdescr.com - Privacy

You are in 2.2M online aggregator.

The bookdescr.com aggregator is a community aiming at collecting and cataloging items descriptions for the most part of scientific, scientific and technical directions, as well as file metadata. In addition to the descriptions, the aggregator contains only links to third-party resources hosted by users. All information posted on the website is collected from publicly available public Internet resources and is intended solely for informational purposes. bookdescr.com - aggregator items is a website that collects and organizes online items from users. Item aggregation is done for fact-finding purposes, and website bookdescr.com respects the rights of copyright holders and respect dcma.

The aggregator bookdescr.com is not responsible for the upload of the items users. Any items will be removed according to the first requirement of the owner or at the request of dcma in 24 hours.

Oh the Supreme Father! Oh the Source of the Universe! Oh the Father of the World, our Strength and Support! Oh compassionate Lord, Gracious to all! Oh the incomparable teacher outside of any tradition! Oh the Supreme Lord! Gracefully send down to us The gift of right thinking, So we can serve humanity And make this world a paradise. 

Dhirendra Brahmachari 

#225d920 2.1.632 

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. This includes your name, email and facebook name (if you opt for it) at the time of registration. We will not post anything to your facebook account without your explicit permission. We do not have access to your passwords or any other info that is meant to be private.

## A responsibility.

The aggregator bookdescr.com is not responsible for the upload of the items users. Any items will be removed according to the first requirement of the owner or at the request of dcma in 24 hours.  

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:   
· To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs  
· To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
· To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
· To send periodic emails about to tell you about new features, offerings, obtain your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with the site. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email  

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information). We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Personally identifiable information not also may be transferred to another entity in the event of a merger, reorganization, bankruptcy or liquidation of assets, sale of assets, or other similar transaction. We may also release your information when we believe release is dont appropriate to comply with the law dcma. we ask you enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, intellectual property and dcma. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy. 

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by sending an email to [bookdescr@tuta.io](mailto:bookdescr@tuta.io)  

## Last Modified

This privacy policy was last modified on January 15, 2019
